cargames60.com 2016-11-04

# Car Games Dirt Bike Games Drag Racing Games Parking Games

| 

CarGames60.com collects some Personal Data cookie from its Users.

The Data are collected and processed for the purposes set out below.

## Data Processing Ownership

CarGames60.com,  

## Types of Data collected

Among the Data that this sitemay collect there are: Cookie and Browsing and usage Data, User Registration Info such as name, and mail. 

## Using the Data obtained

All these data are used to improve our sites and user access feeling. Any date that we collected only use for this site, and not given to others. But the third trusted partner such as Google, Addthis, maybe also collect some data, but of couse they will also obey the privacy rules in the internet.

### Place

The Data are processed at the headquarters of the Data Controller, unless stated otherwise in the rest of this document.

### Conservation Time

The Data are kept for the time necessary to perform the service requested by the User, and the User can always ask for their suspension or removal.

## Detailed information on the processing of Personal Data and the services provided by third parties

Personal Data collected for the following purposes and using the following services:

  * ### Interaction with external social networks and platforms

  * 

## Additional information about data processing

### Legal Protection

The User¡¯s Personal Data may be used for legal purposes by the Owner of the sitein court or in the stages leading to possible legal action arising from its improper use or that of related services by the User. 

### Additional Information

Specific information may be shown on the pages of the Site concerning particular services or the processing of Data provided by the User or by the Data Subject. 

### Maintenance

The User¡¯s Personal Data may be further used in ways and for purposes required for sitemaintenance. 

### System Logs

For operation and maintenance purposes, this siteand any third party services it uses may collect system logs, i.e., files that record interaction ¨C including navigation. They may also contain personal data, such as IP addresses. 

### Information not contained in this policy

More information on processing Personal Information may be requested from the Owner at any time. 

### The Rights of Data Subjects

Those persons to whom the Data refer have the right, at any time, to know whether their data has been stored and can consult the Data Controller to learn about their contents and origin, to verify their accuracy or to ask for them to be supplemented, cancelled, updated or corrected, or for their transformation into anonymous format or to block any data held in violation of the law, as well as to oppose their treatment for any and all legitimate reasons. Requests should be sent to the Owner of the Processing System. 

### Changes to this Privacy Policy

The sitereserves the right to make changes to this Privacy Policy at any time by giving notice to its Users on this page, and by ensuring analogous protection of the Personal Information in all cases. It is strongly recommended to check this page often, referring to the date of the last modification listed at the bottom. 

|   
---|---
